Eyinmosan Sholaye



novertech4@gmail.com



07045459047



linkedin.com/in/eyinmosan-sholaye-080732172

Summary

Hi, a Software developer with 2 years of experience in designing and testing web applications that satisfy business and customer needs. Skilled in directing development with a creative and performance-oriented approach. I'm a forward-thinker, skilled in JavaScript, TypeScript, CSS, SCSS, chakra-UI, React, Next.js, Node.js, and other tools to effectively translate user and business needs into functional software codes.

Experience



nHub

Jul 2022 - Present (9 months)

- * Using tools and methodologies to create representations for functions and user interfaces of the desired product
- * Work with development teams and product managers to ideate software solutions
- * Design client-side and server-side architecture
- * Develop and manage well-functioning databases and applications
- * Write effective APIs
- * Test software to ensure responsiveness and efficiency
- * Troubleshoot, debug and upgrade software
- * Create security and data protection settings

ш

IT Support Specialist

Josts greens services

Jan 2023 - Present (3 months)

maintained and monitored the company website



Community Manager

nHub

Dec 2022 - Present (4 months)

Responsible for building and maintaining the vibrant nHUB community in Jos; working closely with cross-functional teams including Marketing/ media, Technical Support, Developers, Data analysis, entrepreneur, and business people.

A

Steam instructor

9jacodekids Academy

Jul 2018 - Jan 2023 (4 years 7 months)

I teach kids how to code in scratch, python, and lego robotics. also, I guide them on how to think critically and build android apps.



Intern

9jacodekids Academy

Sep 2018 - Feb 2019 (6 months)

learned how to code in scratch, python, and built a website with HTML, CSS, and Javascript. Built and programmed EV3 logo robots

Education



federal university of petroleum resouces

bachelor of phycis, physics 2015 - 2019



Redeemed Christain Fellowship code Bootcap (FUPRE Chapter)

web development, Information Technology

Jun 2017 - Present

Learn how to build my first website with HTML, CSS, and js for responsiveness and also made use of git to host my static page

Skills

Negotiation • Search Engine Optimization (SEO) • Communication • Google Workplace • Microsoft Access • SQL • Social Media • Public Relations • Project Management • Software Installation